

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

#### **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and u "Nội dung, nội dung, nội dung" là nó khiến văn bản giống thật hơn of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

#### **EDUCATION**



#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. mus et iusto odio dignissimos administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult fread, kids). Controversy in the Design World Some claim I and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to dụng nó? Chúng ta vẫn biết rằng, làm việc với một đoạn văn bản dễ đọc và rõ nghĩa dễ gâ goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# **ACTIVITIES**





#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer tin professor at Hampden-Sydney College in Virginia, looked up one of the more 'queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 2004

## **HONORS & AWARDS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO

2013 - 2014

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US rse pains." help@lipsum.com Priv

#### **REFERENCES**



#### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

**U** 01234567890 mbinhnv@topcv.com

#### **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop Excel **English** Power Point • **Japanese** 

### **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt um et dolorum fuga and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities